Guys, my phone is gonna die soon, but I wanted to come and make a quick video to tell you the following
Some people have been texting me saying there is nothing much we can do except protesting and boycotting and praying for you guys
This is not nothing. This is this is great. This is what we're asking you to do
Protest, boycott, pray for us, make donations and keep talking about the palestine cause and about what's happening in palestine
We are asking you to do this. We are asking you to do this. Don't say I don't have much following
So it doesn't matter if I don't speak. It doesn't matter if I don't post. No, it's very important
It's very important to go and protest. It's a way that we, you know
Pressure our governments to to to take an action
So please don't feel like you're not doing anything
You are doing something and what you're doing is actually
Making a difference and making a change in what's happening
Please continue doing what you are doing right now